http://www.castleoaks.org/privacy-policy

Volunteer
Privacy Policy  Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church is committed to protecting your privacy and developing technology that gives you the most powerful and safe online experience. This Statement of Privacy applies to the Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church Web site and governs data collection and usage. By using the Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.Collection of your Personal InformationCastle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used by Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church Web site.Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church does not read any of your private online communications.Castle Oaks Evangelical  Church encourages you to review the privacy statements of Web sites you choose to link to from Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church so that you can understand how those Web sites collect, use and share your information. Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant  is not responsible for the privacy  or other content on Web sites outside of the Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church and Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church family of Web sites.Use of your Personal InformationCastle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church collects and uses your personal information to operate the Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church Web site and deliver the services you have requested. Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church also uses your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church and its affiliates. Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered.Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church keeps track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit within Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church, in order to determine what Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church Web sites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church, or the public.Use of CookiesThe Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church Web site use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church pages, or register with Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church site or services, a cookie helps Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church Web site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church features that you customized.You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church services or Web sites you visit.Security of your Personal InformationCastle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other Web sites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Changes to this StatementCastle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church is protecting your information.Contact InformationCastle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Castle Oaks Evangelical Covenant Church at kspead@castleoaks.org. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
